Henry DeWolf Smyth Papers 1885-1987 Mss.Ms.Coll.15
American Philosophical Society
- Series IX. Reprints, Journals and Publications, 1913-85
  - Horton, Frank and Ann Catherine Davies, May 1922
    Occurrence of ionization by cumulative effects
  - Horton, Frank and Ann Catherine Davies, Nov. 1921
    Production of radiation and ionization by electron bombardment in pure and impure helium
  - Hull, A. W., Oct. 1919
    Position of atoms in metals
  - Hunt, Morton M., 19 Nov. 1949
    Life of an atomic scientist: a detailed report on Princeton's Henry DeWolf Smyth
  - Hunt, Morton M., 1950
    Mr. Atom
    re: HDS corresp., drafts
  - IAEA publications (Box Series IX-5)
    -See International Atomic Energy Agency
  - Imai, Ryukichi, Jul. 1964
    International safeguards
    -See Ser.I, McKnight, Allan Douglas
  - Ingraham, R., 11 Apr. 1956
    Coupling of Boson fields to the matter fields
  - International atom, n.d.
  - International Atomic Energy Agency, Agreements registered with the, 1973
    5th ed.
  - International Atomic Energy Agency Appraisal with recommendations for U.S. policy, 1972
    report to Sec'y of State
  - International Atomic Energy Agency Board of Governors and Permanent Missions, 1964-69
  - International Atomic Energy Agency Bulletin
    - Folder #1, 1964-73
    - Folder #2, 1977; 1984
  - International Atomic Energy Agency IAEA Services and Assistance, 1970; 1973
  - International Atomic Energy Agency Power and research reactors in member states, May 1970
  - International Atomic Energy Agency Presenting Vienna, 1968
    social and travel guide
  - International Atomic Energy Agency The Secretariat. Home addresses and telephone numbers, Dec. 1968
  - International Atomic Energy Agency Statute, 1956-67
  - International Atomic Energy Agency Twenty years, 1957-1977
    20th anniversary
  - International Control of Atomic Energy. Second annual report of the U.N. Atomic Energy Commission to the Security Council, 1947
  - Janes, G. S. and A. R. Kantrowitz, R. M. Patrick, H. E. Petschek, 1958 (Box Series IX-6)
    Shock waves in high temperature plasmas
    -See Ser.I, Geneva Conference. Committee to read papers
    AVCO Research Lab. abstract
  - Jauncey, G. E. M., 1926
    Scattering of x-rays: a review
  - Johnson, James R. and Hans Thurnauer, 16 Apr. 1956
    Integrated Atomic Energy Program
  - Journal of the Washington Academy of Sciences, 19 Oct. 1917; 19 Sep. 1920
    v.7, n.17; v.10, n.15
  - Kallmann, H. and B. Rosen, 30 May 1930
    Elektronenaustausch langsamer Ionen II.
  - Kallmann, H. and B. Rosen, 4 Aug. 1929
    Ionisations- und Dissoziations- vorgänge in einfachen gasen
  - Kallmann, H. and B. Rosen, 6 Dec. 1929
    Über die Elementarvorgänge bei Ionen- und Elektronenstoss
  - Kalven, Harry, Jr., 1954
    Case of J. Robert Oppenheimer
    Bull. of the Atomic Scientists issue on JRO
  - Kapitza, P. L., 28 Jul. 1924
    N1-ray tracks in a strong magnetic field
  - Kapitza, P. L., 1922
    Loss of energy of an α-ray beam in its passage through matter. Part I - Passage through air and CO2
  - Kapitza, P. L., 9 Apr. 1924
    Method of producing strong magnetic fields
  - Kapitza, P. L., 14 Nov. 1922
    Note on the curved tracks of α-particles
  - Kapitza, P. L., May 1923
    On the theory of N4-radiation
  - Kapitza, P. [L.] and H. W. B. Skinner, 23 Aug. 1924
    Zeeman effect in strong magnetic fields
  - Kapitza. P. [L.] and H. W. B. Skinner, 25 Jul. 1925
  - Keepin, G. R., 25 Jul. 1966
    Detection, identification and analysis of fissionable isotopes based on differential group yields and spectra of delayed fission neutrons
  - Kennan, George F., Apr. 1956
    History and diplomacy as viewed by a diplomatist
  - Kennan, George F., May 1953
    Training for statesmanship
    in The Atlantic
  - Keussler, Victor V., 13 Jan. 1922
    Über die Art der Anregung des Atom- und Molekülspektrums von Wasserstoff durch Elektronenstoss
  - Kipphardt, Heinar, Jul. 1968
    In the matter of J. Robert Oppenheimer
    theater program
  - Kissinger, Henry A., Feb. 1957
    Diplomacy and the limitation of armaments [Chapter 10 - Study Group on Nuclear Weapons and Foreign Policy]
    -See Ser.I, Kissinger, Henry
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1956
    Force and diplomacy in the nuclear age
    -See Ser.I, Council on Foreign Relations
  - Klaw, Spencer, 7 Oct. 1960
    The `New' Professors
    Alumni Weekly
  - Koernicke, Erich, 24 May 1925
    Bestimmung der Dissoziationswärme von Quecksilbermolekülen aus den Bandespektren des Quecksilberdampfes
  - Kolb, A. C., Jun. 1958
    Magnetic compression of shock preheated deuterium
  - Komelkov, V. S., 30 Jul. 1958
    Plasma motion of powerful discharges in the current's proper magnetic field
  - Kopfermann, H., 1924
    Über sensibilisierte Fluoreszenz von Blei- und Wismutdampf
  - Kouts, Herbert J. and James M. Williams, 5 Aug. 1969
    U. S. safeguards systems studies
  - Kronig, R. deL., Oct. 1926
    Dielectric constant of symmetrical polyatomic dipole-gases on the new quantum mechanics
  - Kronig, R. deL. and I. I. Rabi, Feb. 1927
    Symmetrical top in the undulatory mechanics
  - Kuznetzov, I. V., 1948
    Concerning a faulty interpretation of the 2nd Law of Thermodynamics
    translated transcript
  - Lange, H. W. Victor
    Vanishing ivory tower
    -See Klaw, Spencer. The `New' Professors
  - Langmuir, Irving
  - Laurence, William L., [1945?]
    Story of the atomic bomb
    reprints of NY Times' articles
  - Lavatelli, L. S., 17 Mar. 1943
    Metal sources of the 8b 3 isotron
    OSRD Report #42 photos
  - Levi, Edward H., [1945]
    General summary [of Senate Bill 1463, proposed Atomic Energy Act of 1945]
    -See Ser. II, Johnson and May bills for control of atomic energy
  - Libby, W[illard] F., n.d.
    Radiation dosages from natural radioactivities and cosmic radiation
  - Lilienthal, David E.
  - Lilienthal, David E., n.d.
    Case for candor on national security
  - Lilienthal, David E. and H. D. Smyth, Cord Meyer, Jr., Jul. 1946
    Stopping the atomic armament race
    -See also Ser. VIII, Stopping the atomic armament race: what we are up against
  - Lippmann, Walter
  - Lozier, W. Wallace, 15 Aug. 1934
    Heat of dissociation of CO and the electron affinity of O
  - Luce, J. S., Jun. 1958
    Studies of intense gas discharges
  - Masters, Dexter and Katharine May One world or none, 1946
    Arnold, H. H.
    Bohr, Niels
    Einstein, Albert
    Langmuir, Irving
    Lippmann, Walter
    Morrison, Philip
    Oppenheimer, J. R.
    Ridenour, Louis
    Shapley, Harlow
    Szilard, Leo
    Urey, Harold
    Young, Gale
    report on atomic bomb and arms race
  - McDuffie, Bruce, 5 Oct. 1942
    Attempted preparation of tuballoy hexacarbonyl
    OSRD Report #21
  - McDuffie, Bruce, 29 Jul. 1942
    Possibility of using liquid ammonia as solvent in the preparation of tubanous salts
    OSRD Report #16
  - McDuffie, B[ruce] and A. D. Schellenberg, R. W. Thompson, J. B. White, 14 Jul. 1942
    Memorandum on preparation of TuI4
    OSRD Report #15 diagrams
  - McMahon, Brien, 25 Sep. [1945]
    Controlling atomic energy
    atomic energy bill
  - Mackay, Charles A., Oct. 1924
    Ionizing potentials of multiatomic gases
  - Mannkopff, Reinhold, 4 Feb. 1926
    Über die AuslC6schung der Resonanzfluoreszenz von Natriumdampf
  - Meers, Dale R., 6 Jun. 1968
    Communist child care programs: innovation and Pandora's box
  - Marshak, Robert E., 1963
    Reexamining the Soviet scientific challenge
    -See Ser.II, Council on Foreign Relations. Science and Foreign Policy Study Group. Reports
  - Menke, John R., [1947?]
    Nuclear fission as a source of power
    -See Ser.II, Social Science Research Council. Committee on Social Aspects of Atomic Energy
  - Meyer, Cord, Jr., 1946
    Stopping the atomic armament race: what are the chances
    -See Ser.VIII, Stopping the atomic armament race: what we are up against
    -See Ser.IX, Lilienthal, David E., Stopping the atomic armament race
    proofs
    article
  - Michigan State University. Dept. of Physics, 12 June 1964
    Nuclear physics program of the Michigan State University Cyclotron, Proposal to the National Science Foundation for support of the
  - Mohler, F. L. and Paul D. Foote, 17 Dec. 1921
    Characteristic soft x-rays from arcs in gases and vapors
    Sci. Papers of the Bur. of Standards; 425
  - Mohler, F. L. and Paul D. Foote, 19 Mar. 1920
    Ionization and resonance potentials of nitrogen, oxygen and hydrogen
  - Mohler, F. L. and Paul D. Foote, 14 Oct. 1920
    Ionization and resonance potentials of some nonmetallic elements
    Sci. Papers of the Bur. of Standards; 400
  - Morrison, Philip
  - Morse, Philip M. and E. C. G. Stueckelberg, Jun. 1929
    Diatomic molecules according to the wave mechanics. I. Electronic levels of the hydrogen molecular ion
  - Morse, Philip M., 1 Jul. 1929
    Diatomic molecules according to the wave mechanics. II. Vibrational levels
  - Nakicenovic, Slobodan, Jun. 1971 (Box Series IX-7)
    Impact of the NPT safeguards agreement on the safeguards operations of the IAEA
  - Nassau Sovereign, Mar. 1939
    v.1, n.5; article on HDS
  - Nature: a weekly illustrated journal of science, 11 Nov. 1922
    n.2767, v.110; review of HDS paper
  - Nature, 16 Jul. 1923
    n.2798, v.111
  - Nature, 26 Jul. 1924
    n.2856, v.114
  - Newman, Steven L., 1972
    Flight mission 1954: "Axe out Oppenheimer"
  - New Republic. 25th anniversary number. Part 2, 8 Nov. 1939
  - New Yorker, 31 Aug. 1946
    Hiroshima
  - Nordheim, L. W., n.d.
    Remarks on the future development of Project and Nucleonics
  - Nuclear India, Aug. 1969
    v.7, n.12
  - Nuclear Industry, Nov. 1974
    v.21, n.11
  - Nuclear News, 1972
    v.15, n.12; re: Nuclear Statesman
  - Olum, Paul, 22 Apr. 1942
    Brief report on sputtering
    OSRD Report #10
  - Olum, Paul, 4 Mar. 1943
    Evaluation of the influence of space charge on the operation of the isotron
    OSRD Report #38
  - Olum, P[aul], n.d.
    Report on literature on mass spectrographic methods of isotope separation
    autograph ms.
  - Olum, Paul, 26 Jan. 1943
    Simultaneous use of several different kinds of ions
    OSRD Report #28
  - O'Neill, Gerard K., 13 Apr. 1956
    Storage-ring Synchrotron - a device for high energy physics research
    -See Ser. I, American Physical Society
  - Operation Castle (Joint Task Force Seven), 1954
    -See Ser. III, Operation Castle
  - Operation Greenhouse (Joint Task Force Three), 1951
    -See Ser. III, Operation Greenhouse
  - Oppenheimer, J. R[obert]
  - [Oppenheimer, J. Robert], 1964
    Reviews of Modern Physics
    60th birthday commemorative issue
  - [Oppenheimer, J. Robert], 1954
    Security Board reports on Dr. Oppenheimer
    Bull. of Atomic Scientists. Special Section
  - Pais, A., 1977
    Radioactivity's two early puzzles
    -See Ser. VIII, "The `Smyth Report' " [Princeton University Library Chronicle]
  - Peace and the sciences, 1966
    (International Institute for Peace)
    Emelyanov, V. S.
  - Peery, L. C. and D. S. Webster
    Applications of radioactive tracer techniques in experimental chemical engineering
    -See Ser. II, Mulliken Comm.
  - Physics Today, " A memorial to Oppenheimer", Oct. 1967
    v.20, n.10
  - Princeton Alumni Weekly, 13 Jan. 1941
    v.41, n.13
  - Princeton Alumni Weekly, Sep. 1945
    v.46, n.2; "Princeton and Atomic Energy"
  - Princeton Alumni Weekly, Nov. 1945
    v.46, n.7; "Semi-technical" p.6
  - Princeton Alumni Weekly, 13 Feb. 1948
    v.48, n.18; "Physics at Princeton"
  - Princeton University. Graduate Council., 7 Nov. 1952
    Excerpts from the Proceedings of the Fall Meeting
  - Princeton University., 1946
    Handbook for Princeton clubs and alumni associations
  - Princeton University Library Chronicle, 1976
    -See also Ser. VIII, "The `Smyth Report' " [Princeton University Library Chronicle]
  - Princeton University. Official Register., 1 Oct. 1952
    v.44, n.3; financial rpt.
  - Proposal for an Institute of Biochemistry and Biophysics of Princeton University, [1946-49]
    Harvey, E. M.
  - Proposal for nuclear physics contract between Princeton University and the AEC, 1950-51
  - Proposed 300 GeV Accelerator, Jan. 1968
    -See Ser. I, Universities Research Association, Inc.
  - Questions and answers about atomic energy
  - Rabi, I. I.
  - Report on the international control of atomic energy, 1946
    Barnard, Chester I.
    Byrnes, James F.
    Thomas, Charles A.
    Winne, Harry A.
  - Ridenour, Louis
  - Ridenour, Louis N., Nov. 1945
    Military security & the atomic bomb
  - Robinson, H. R., Jul. 1925
    X-ray terms and intensities
  - Russell, George, 3. Jun. 1985
    Who has the bomb?
    photocopy
  - Salam, Abdus, Feb. 1968
    United Nations and the International World of Physics
    -See Ser. IV, International Centre for Theoretical Physics [Trieste]
  - Sampson, M. B., 3 Jan. 1943
    Report of work on the 12-inch tube 19-26 Dec. 1942
    OSRD Report #27
  - Saturday Review, 2 Oct. 1965
    nuclear tech.
  - Schwartz, Judah L. and E. Raymond Platig, 1963
    Science appreciation and literacy for the international relations generalist
    -See Ser. II, Council on Foreign Relations. Science and Foreign Policy Study Group. Reports
  - Seaborg, Glenn T., 16 Nov. 1945
    Chemical and radioactive properties of the heavy elements
    transcript of talk
  - Scheinman, Lawrence, 1985
    Nonproliferation role of the IAEA
  - Schelberg, A. and R. W. Thompson Saturated vapour pressures of TuCl4, TuBr4, and TuI4, 10 Oct. 1942
    OSRD Report #24 diagrams
  - Schelberg, A. D. and R. W. Thompson, J. E. White, 1 Nov. 1942
    Characteristics of an arc in tuballoy tetrahalide vapour Folders #1-3
    OSRD Report #36
    photos, diagrams
  - Schmid, R., 21 Jan. 1936
    Zur Deutung der Elektronenstoss-versuche an CO und Konsequenzen bezüglich der Bindungsenergie-werte C-C und H-C auf Grund der Annahme: D (CO)=6.9 Volt
  - Schmidt, Erich, 18 Jan. 1925
    Über ein Absorptionsspektrum des Luftsauerstoffs im äusserstein Ultraviolett
  - Segre, Emilio and Edwin M. McMillan, Joseph W. Kennedy, Arthur C. Wahl
    Account of the discovery and early study of element 94
    -See Ser. V, Envelope 1, Seitz, Frederick
  - Seitz, Frederick
  - Shapley, Harlow (Box Series IX-8)
  - Shapley, Harlow, 1954
    Cosmography: an approach to orientation
    -See Ser. I, Oates, Whitney J.
  - Shenstone, Allen G., 24 Feb. 1961
    Princeton & physics
  - Shenstone, Allen G.
    Sixty years of physics at Princeton
    -See Ser. II, Physics at Princeton
  - Shepley, James R. and Clay Blair, Jr., 24 Sep. 1954
    Hydrogen Bomb: how the U. S. almost lost it
    U.S. News and World Report
  - Sinelnikov, K.D. and P.M. Zeidlitz, Ja.B. Feinberg, L.V. Doubovoy, A.M. Necrashevich, O.G. Zagorodov, E.I. Lutsenko, B.G. Safronov, N.V. Topolya, 12 Aug. 1955
    Experiments on electron resonance and wave guide properties of plasma
  - Skolnikoff, Eugene B., Nov. 1966
    Scientific advice in the State Department
  - Smith, Alice Kimball, Oct. 1958
    Behind the decision to use the atomic bomb: Chicago 1944-45
    Bull. of the Atomic Sci.
  - Smith, Datus C., Jr., 1976
    The publishing history of the "Smyth Report"
    -See Ser.IX, Princeton University Library Chronicle
  - Smith, Gerard C., Apr. 1984
    Arms control and disarmament agency: an unfinished history
  - Smith, L. G., 31 Dec. 1942
    Report of work on the twelve inch isotron
    OSRD Report #26
  - Smith, L. G., 1 Oct. 1942
    Summary of work on the twelve inch isotron
    OSRD Report #22
  - Smith, L. G., 1 Oct. 1942 - 15 Feb. 1943
    OSRD Report #32
  - Smith, Lloyd P., n.d.
    Preliminary report on electromagnetic method for the separation of isotopes
  - Smyth, Charles Henry, Jr., 1927
    Genesis of alkaline rocks
  - Smyth, H. D.
    -See Ser.II, Council on Foreign Relations. Nuclear Weapons and Foreign Policy Study Group. Reports
  - Smyth, H. D., 1924
    Application of positive ray analysis to ionization problems
  - Smyth, H. D., 1928
    -See Condon, E[dward] U.
  - Smyth, H. D., Apr. 1954
    Development of nuclear power for peaceful purposes
    -See also Ser.VIa, Development of nuclear power for peaceful purposes
  - Smyth, H. D., 1956
  - Smyth, H. D., 1954
    Dissenting opinion of HDS in the matter of J. Robert Oppenheimer
    -See Ser.VIII, Dissenting...
    in U.S. AEC "Statement by the AEC"
  - Smyth, H. D. and K. T. Compton, Dec. 1920
    Effect of fluorescence and dissociation on the ionizing potential of iodine vapor
    -See also, Compton, K. T. Fluorescence, dissociation...
  - Smyth, H. D., 1946
    Fifty years of atomic physics
    -See also Ser.VIa, Fifty years of atomic physics
    -See also Ser.VIa, Sigma Xi lecture
    -See also Ser.IX, Atomic energy and its implications, Symposium on
  - Smyth, H. D.
    -See Compton, K. T.
  - Smyth, H. D., 1947
    From x-rays to nuclear fission
  - Smyth, H. D., 5 Dec. 1923
    Further studies in ionization: hydrogen and oxygen
  - Smyth, H. D., 1 May 1953
    Future of research and development
    -See also Ser.VIa, Future of research and development
  - Smyth, H. D., 20 Jun. 1923
    Ionisation of nitrogen by electron impact
  - Smyth, H. D. and E. C. G. Stueckelberg, 1 Aug. 1930
    Ionization of carbon dioxide by electron impact
    reprint corrected June 1931
  - Smyth, H. D. and J. P. Blewett Ionization of carbon disulfide by electron impact, 15 Aug. 1934
  - Smyth, H. D. and E. C. G. Stueckelberg
    Ionization of nitrous oxide and nitrogen dioxide by electron impact
    -See Smyth, H. D. Ionization of carbon dioxide by electron impact
  - Smyth, H. D. and D. W. Mueller, 15 Jan. 1933
    Ionization of water vapor by electron impact
  - Smyth, H. D. and R. R. Wilson, 1942
    Isotron method
    OSRD Report #18
  - Smyth, H. D., Mar. 1946
    Lesson of atomic energy
    Infantry Journal
  - Smyth, H. D. and Charles W. Ufford
    Matter, motion, and electricity. Answers to problems
    3rd impression
  - Smyth, H. D., 29 Jul. 1950
    National security and the scientist
  - Smyth, H. D., 9 Aug. 1922
    New method for studying ionising potentials
  - Smyth, H. D., May 1955
    New responsibilities of physicists
  - Smyth, H. D., Oct. 1956
    Nuclear power and foreign policy
  - Smyth, H. D., Spring 1967
    Oppenheimer's contributions
  - Smyth, H. D.
    Physics at Princeton
    -See Princeton Alumni Weekly (13 Feb. 1948)
  - Smyth, H. D., Jul. 1950
    Place of science in a free society
  - Smyth, H. D., 1955
    Place of science in contemporary society
    -See also Ser.VIa, Place of science in contemporary society
    Ware lecture
  - Smyth, H. D., Dec. 1952
    Present and future activities of the U.S.AEC as they affect mining
  - Smyth, H. D. and E. C. G. Stueckelberg
    Primäre und sekundäre Ionen in Sauerstoff und Kohlendioxyd
  - Smyth, H. D., 1924
    [Primary and secondary products of ionization in hydrogen]
  - Smyth, H. D., Apr. 1925
    Primary and secondary products of ionization in hydrogen
  - Smyth, H. D., Jul. 1931
    Products and processes of ionization by low speed electrons
  - Smyth, H. D., 1919
    Radiating potentials of nitrogen
  - Smyth, H. D. and Creutz, E. Wigner, 9 Apr. 1942
    Review of some of the organizational difficulties in the S-1 Project
  - Smyth, H. D., Jul. 1955
    Science in contemporary society
    -See also Ser.IX, Smyth H. D., Place of science in contemporary society
  - Smyth, H. D., 16 May 1962
    Science's answer: fact or guess?
  - Smyth, H. D. and C. J. Brasefield, 31 May 1926
    Secondary spectrum of hydrogen and the occurrence of H3+
  - Smyth, H. D.
    - Folder #1, 1945
      Lithoprint version with note "HDS Private Copy #2"
    - Folders #2-3, 1945
      Lithoprint ver.
  - Smyth, H. D. (Box Series IX-9)
    - Folder #4, 1945
  - Smyth, H. D., 1976
    "The `Smyth Report' "
    -See Ser. VIII, "The `Smyth Report' " [Princeton Univ. Lib. Chronicle]
    Princeton Univ. Library Chronicle article
  - Smyth, H. D., 14 Oct. 1925
    Some experiments on collisions of the second kind
  - Smyth, H. D., 22 May 1959
    Sponsored research - millions of dollars for the "Hire Learning" raise problems of policy
  - Smyth, H. D., Feb. 1951
    Stockpiling and rationing of scientific manpower
    AAAS address
  - Smyth, H. D.
    -See Lilienthal, David E.
  - Smyth, H. D., 1962
    This science knows - and this it guesses
  - Smyth, H. D., 20 Nov. 1936
    Useless research
  - Smyth, H. D., Feb. 1946
    We face a new age
  - Social Science Research Council Items, Mar. 1947
  - Stix, T. H., 1 Jul. 1958
    Generation and thermolization of plasma waves
  - Stix, T. H. and R. W. Palladino, 1 Jul. 1958
    Experiments on ion cyclotron resonance
  - Stopping the spread of nuclear weapons, 1967
  - Strauss, Lewis L., 1962
    Men and decisions
    reviews
  - Strauss, Lewis L., Jul. 1962
    Safeguarding our atomic secrets
    Sat. Evening Post
  - Stuart, H. A., Mar. 1925
    Über die AuslC6schung der Resonanzfluoreszenz bei Quecksilberdampf
  - Stueckelberg, E. C. G., 1 Jul. 1929
    Simultaneous ionization and dissociation of oxygen and intensities of the ultra-violet O2+
  - Sullivan, Walter, 9 Jan. 1966
    Giant among atom smashers
    -See Ser.II, High Energy Physics Policy Statements
  - Sutton, Roger B., 9 Mar. 1943
    4 1/2" isotron
    OSRD Report #23 diagrams
  - Sutton, R. B. and R. W. Thompson, 1 Apr. 1942
    Preliminary study of the relative abundance of the ions Tu+, TuCl+, TuCl2+, TuCl3+, and TuCl4+ in a discharge of TuCl4 vapor
    OSRD Report #6
  - Szilard, Leo
  - Takamine, T., 19 Mar. 1926
    Intensität der Verbotenen Quecksilberlinie (λ2270 Å)
  - Technology behind investment, Oct. 1956
    (Arthur D. Little, Inc.)
    -See Ser.I, Bank of New York
    n.3
  - Teller, E[dward], 15 Jun. 1941
    On the possibility of fission for higher elements
  - Thomas, Charles A.
  - Thompson, R. W., 6 Jan. 1942
    Mass-spectrographic analysis of electron-controlled arc source
    OSRD Report #3
  - Thompson, R. W., 10 Oct. 1942
    Production of tuballoy metal for an isotron plant I
    OSRD Report #25
  - Thompson, R. W., 22 Apr. 1942
    Tuballoy oxide ions in a metallic tuballoy discharge
    OSRD Report #9
  - Thompson, R. W. and A. Schelberg, 4 May 1942
    Vapor pressure of TuCl4 and TuBr4
    OSRD Report #11 diagrams
  - Thompson, R. W. and J. E. White, 21 Jun. 1942
    Mass spectrometer investigation of vibrator ion source
    OSRD Report #14
  - Thompson, S. G. and A. Ghiorso, B. G. Harvey, G. R. Choppin Transcurium isotopes produced in the neutron irradiation of plutonium, 10 Dec. 1953
    UCRL-2433
  - Time, 25 Dec. 1939
    v.34, n.26
  - Time, 20 Aug. 1945
    v.46, n.8; A-bomb
  - Time, 4 Jun. 1951
    v.57, n.23
  - Time, 14 Jan. 1952
    v.59, n.2; Gordon Dean
  - Time, 21 Sep. 1953
    v.62, n.12; Lewis Strauss
  - Tolman, Richard C. and E.B. Vliet, W.McG. Peirce, R.H. Dougherty Disappearance of smoke in a confined space, 7 Dec. 1918
  - Tolman, R[ichard] C. and L. H. Reyerson, E. B. Vliet, R. H. Gerke, A. P. Brooks, 7 Dec. 1918
    Relation between the intensity of Tyndall beam and concentration of suspensions and smokes
  - Tolman, Richard C., Apr. 1944
    Thermodynamics with relations to statistical mechanics and with applications to steady states: the principles of thermodynamics
  - Tolman, Richard C. and Elmer B. Vliet, 7 Dec. 1918
    Tyndallmeter for the examination of disperse systems
  - Tooling and production. Nuclear power no threat to technological unemployment, Jun. 1954
  - Treaty establishing the European Atomic Energy Community (EURATOM) and connected documents, [1957?]
  - Trytten, M. H., 8 Sep. 1950
    Coverage of scientific personnel in American Men of Science, Eighth Edition
  - Turner, Louis A., 1 & 15 Apr. 1946
    Atomic energy from U238
    -See Ser.I, Turner, Louis A.
    Letter to the editor, Physical Rev., submitted 29 May 1940